Vyacheslav Titov

.NET Core Developer

rincew1nd

in rincew1nd

79689853691

04 Apr 1994



PROFILE

.NET Core/Framework developer with 4+ years of developing and 3+ years of testing web applications and worker services. Primarily focused on application refactoring (migration from framework to core, code optimization), service integration, data processing. Worked with different methodologies (TDD, DDD, BDD), primarily using Agile (Scrum).

LANGUAGES

Russian **English** C2

EDUCATION

2014 - Jul 2017 **Bachelor of Science** Moscow, Russia

Moscow Technological University ☑

Area: Computer Science, Software engineer

GPA: 3.2

SKILLS

- .NET Core 2/3, ASP.NET MVC
- .NET WebApi, Background Services
- Unit Testing (xUnit, nUnit, Selenium)
- Relation databases (Microsoft SQL Server/ PostgreSQL, Oracle Database))
- Data access (EF Core 2/3, Dapper, ADO.NET) + LINQ

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sep 2020 - present

.NET Developer

Moscow, Russia

ZAO "Action-Media" □

- Development of new features for the application, architecture solutions for microservices, and bug fixing.
- Microservice refactoring for lower consumption of CPU and memory resources
- Business requirement analysis, task decomposition, and assessment (in working hours)

Sep 2018 - Sep 2020

.NET Developer

Moscow, Russia

000 "IBS" □

- Complete projects migration from .net framework 4.5 to .net
- Developing and refactoring of background workers for processing events from CRM
- Data importing service from client's 1C for NeocaseCRM (Windows Service, Reddis, Microsoft SQL Server, Dapper)
- Introduction of a code review process

May 2017 - Sep 2018 Developer Moscow, Russia OOO "Avon Beauty Products Company" ☑ • Developing and refactoring of .net background workers for mail Developing OracleDB procedures, features for ConcordeXAL **CRM** • Introduction of a code review process, CI/DI (Jenkins) and version control (GitLab) **Automation Tester** May 2015 - Nov 2016 Moscow, Russia ZAO "Action-Media" □ • Developing a test framework based on Selenium driver for C# • Developing unit tests with nUnit and SpecFlow • Conducting automation testing of an asp.net web application • Designing automated test cases **Performance Tester** Oct 2014 - May 2015 Moscow, Russia 000 "S&T international" Conducting load testing of web application Designing of load test cases (HP LoadRunner) • Analysis of test case coverage Apr 2014 - Oct 2014 **Test Designer** Moscow, Russia 000 "S&T international" · Conducting manual testing Designing test cases based on software/feature documentations

• Preparation of test plans, test data